Ralph E. Flanders Papers
Ralph E. Flanders Papers
- Business correspondence Ffles
  - Business correspondence, 1931-1933
    - Wellesley Summer Institute (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Wendt, Edwin R. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Wetherill, Lynn (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Whitehead, R. H. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Whittemore, N. L. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Whittlesy House (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Wilgus, William J. (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Willits, Joseph H. (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Winant, John G. (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Winterrowd, W. H. (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Wisler, Willis (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Wolfe, Albert B. (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Wolfe, Ernest J. (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Wolman, Leo (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Wood, William A. (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Wood, Rawson L. (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Woodbury, W. H. (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Wooster, Harvey A. (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - World Peace Foundation (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Wright, Roy V. (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Yarnall, D. Robert (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Yenching University, Peiping, China (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Business correspondence, 1933-1934
    - Business Advisory and Planning Council
      - Correspondence re: Atlantic Monthly article, Nov. 1933 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence re: Business Week article, 1933 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence re: "Suggested elements of a social and economic platform for business", April, 1934 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Meetings (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Bulletins Relating to Government & Business (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Bullitt, William C. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Bullock, William E. (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Bureau of Foreign & Domestic Commerce (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Business Week, Glen Griswold, Publishing Director (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Butler, Hugh (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Carey, William Wallace (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Chamber of Commerce of United States (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Cherrington, George H. (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Chesterman, F. J. (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Chief of Protocol (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Clark, Evans (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Clark, Wallace (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Cleveland Trust Company (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Codes, Proposed for Machinery & Allied Products Institute (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Coes, Harold V. (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Coil, E. (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Columbia University (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Committee for the Establishment of a Free Gold Market (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Committee for the Nation (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Decentralization of Industry (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Committee of Subsistence Homesteads (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Compton, Karl T. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Compton, Wilson (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Conant, Larry (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Condit, Kenneth H. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Couper, W. J. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Cox, A. B. (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Coyle, David Cushman (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Creighton, Albert M. (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Crowther, Samuel (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Custard, Harry L. (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Czerwonky, Hugo (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Dahlbert, Arthur (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Davies, C. E. (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Day, Edmund (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Denham, Robert Scudder (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Dennison, Henry S. (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Dickinson, H. C. (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Dickinson, John (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Debrul, Ernest F. (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - DuPont, Pierce S. (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Durable Goods Industries Committee (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Eaton, Howard O. (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Economic Forum (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Eliot, Charles W., 2nd. (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Evans, Robert F. (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - (Roberts) Everett Associates (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Fahey, John H. (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Farrell, James A. (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Feiker, Frederick M. (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Filene, Lincoln (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - First National Bank of Boston (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Firth, Norman D. (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Fisher, Irving (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Foster, William T. (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Frey, John (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Gay, Leon S. (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - General Welfare Tax League (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Gerard, James W. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Givens, Merideth (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Gleason, James E. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Gow, J. Steele (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - The Guilds of America Foundation (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Hansen, Alvin H. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Harmon, Dudley (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Harriman, Henry I. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Harriman, William A. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Harris Trust Company (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Harrison, A. Dex (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Harwood, E. C. (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Hathaway, King (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Heimann, Henry H. (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Henn, E. C. (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Hewitt, Fred (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Heyniger, C. L. (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Hindley, Howard (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Hook, James W. (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Horne, Richard C., Jr. (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Horner, Leonard S. (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Hotel Reservations (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Howe, Frederic C. (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Hueber, Paul (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Huffman, E. W. G. (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Ickes, Harold L. (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Industrial Advisory Board (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Industrial Recovery Act (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Javits, Benjamin A. (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Johnson, Hugh S. (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Jordan, Virgil (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Julian, William A. (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Kelley, Robert F. (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Kemper, W. T. (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Kendall, H. P. (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Kendrick, Benjamin B. (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Kiplinger Letters, Notes on (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Kittredge, John W. (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Kolodziej, Paul K. (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Kreps, Theodore (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Lamb, Robert Keen (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Lamond, William H. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Lee, Wilson H. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Leeds, Morris E. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Leigh, Robert D. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Leong, Y. S. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - LePage, C. B. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Lesor, Stanley (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Lewis, David J. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Lewisohn, Sam A. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Lillard, W. P. (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Lind, Herman H. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Lingham, Fred J. (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Lorwin, Lewis L. (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Lund, Robert L. (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Lyon, Leverett S. (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - MacDonald, K. G. (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - MacMillian, Campbell (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Marchant, T. M. (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - McCarthy, W. F. (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - McDonald, Frederick H. (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - McInnerney, Thomas (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Mechanical Engineering Pamphlet (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Merriam, Charles E. (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Meyer, Eugene (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Millikin, Carroll L. (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Milliken, Kent (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Minnesota, University of (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Mitchell, Wesley C. (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Mitchell, William N. (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Moody, Walter S. (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Morgan, H. A. (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Morgan, J. P. (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Morgan, Thomas A. (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Morris, Robert (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Munday, H. D. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Muir, Malcolm (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Nation's Business (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - National Association of Cost Accountants (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - National Civic Federation (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - National Cyclopedia of American Biography (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - National Machine Tool Builders' Association (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - National Recovery Administration (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - National Research Council (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - New England Council (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - New York Times (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Newman, Douglas (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Nienstaedt, L. R. (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Nolen, John (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Norman, Carl A. (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Norris, Alfred G. (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Orton, Vrest (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Oxholm, Axel H. (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Pearson, John (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Peaslee, W. D. A. (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Peters, Arthur C. (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Polakov, Walter N. (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Prentice, Donald B. (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Rabinoff, Max (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Rastall, Walter H. (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Raymond, Fairfield E. (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Reymond, M. H. (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Richberg, Donald A. (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Roper, Daniel C. (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Rukeyser, Merryle Stanley (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - Sachs, Alexander (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - St. Lawrence, John (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - Sales Management (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Schechter, Frank I. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Scovell, Wellington & Company (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Sedwick, Ellery (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Shaviro, Nathan (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Sheedy, Joseph E. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Sherry, F. P. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Shewhart, W. A. (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Shoudy, William A. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Slichter, Dr. Sumner H. (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Social Science Research Council (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Sprague, Oliver M. W. (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - State Recovery Boards (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Stetson, George A. (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Stevens Institute (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Swope, Gerard (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Taylor, Myron C. (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Taylor Society (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Tangeman, W. W. (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Teagle, Walter C. (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Thompson, Sanford E. (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Thorp, Willard L. (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Tupper, E. A. (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Turnbull, William F. (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Tydings, Millard E. (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - United States Department of Commerce (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Vandiest, Edmund C. (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Von Szeliski, Victor (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Voorhees, Stephen F. (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Wagner, Robert F. (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Waite, H. M. (Box 83, Folder 31)
    - Wallace, Henry A. (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - Wallace, L. W. (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - Wardwell, Charles A. R. (Box 83, Folder 34)
    - Weber, Orlando F. (Box 83, Folder 35)
    - Webster, J. E. (Box 83, Folder 36)
    - Wellesley Institute (Box 83, Folder 37)
    - Whaley-Eaton Service (Box 83, Folder 38)
    - Willits, Joseph H. (Box 83, Folder 39)
    - Wilt, A. D., Jr. (Box 83, Folder 40)
    - Wilson, M. L. (Box 83, Folder 41)
    - Wisconsin, University of (Box 83, Folder 42)
    - Witters, Harry (Box 83, Folder 43)
    - Wolman, Leo (Box 83, Folder 44)
    - Wooster, Harvey A. (Box 83, Folder 45)
    - Wright, Roy V. (Box 83, Folder 46)
- Engineering resources and patent materials
  - Administrative Management, Report of President's Committee (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - American Economic Council
    - New Plans (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Criticisms (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - President, Letter to (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Report of (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Statements (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Business Advisory Council
    - Mr. Batt's Committee (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Legislation (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Reports (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - General (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Pacific Steamship (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Cleveland Trust Company Business Bulletin (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Cunard Steamship (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Davis, Harvey N., Stevens Institute of Technology (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Dollar Line Steamship (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - European Trip (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Experimental
    - Drum Cam Cross Feed (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Turret Clamp (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - 2 1/4 Turret-Lathe-Fixed Head, Cam Operated Sliding Gears (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Turret Lathe, Hardened Cone Friction Clutches (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Turret Lathe, Large Friction on Spindle (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Turret Lathe, Twelve Forward, Six Reverse (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - 3 ½ Turret Lathe, 18 Speed Head, Hydraulic Fast Motion (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Fast Motion Pumps
    - Geared Pump as Motor, No. 1 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - 2 Pumps, No. 2 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - 1 Pump, Double By-Pass, No. 3 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Variable pressure relief valve, No. 4 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Finanzamt Moabit West, Berlin, Germany (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - First National Bank, Springfield, Vermont (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Goddard College, Vermont Committee, A-Z (Box 85, Folder 21-41)
  - Holland American Line (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Hydraulic Drive for Grinder Tables (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Hydraulic Shaper (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Hydraulic Turret Lathes
    - First Double Spindle with Hydraulic Feed (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Hydraulic Turret Lathe, Cylinder Under Head (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Hydraulic Turret Lathe, Full Automatic (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Hydraulic, Miscellaneous
    - Automatic Dwell (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Hydraulic Circuit (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Hydraulic Spindle Drive with Variable Capacity Motors (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Mullers Leakage (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Shaper (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Thread Grinder (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Valve Control of Meter Pressure (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Rehabilitation Committee (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Legislation (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous blueprints (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous equipment
    - Forkhardt Chucks (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Machine Tool Builders, Drawing Changes (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Machine Tool Exposition, Ralph E. Flanders (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Meter (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Method & Machine for Grinding Chasers (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Reports (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - National Screw Thread Commission Minutes (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Patent Applications (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Personal Data (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Pumps
    - Accumulator Operating F.M. & Feed Pumps, 2 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Using Accumulator & Mechanical Speed Change, 3 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - By-Pass Valves Hydraulic Operated By Accumulator, 4 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - No Accumulator, By-Pass Pressure Operated, 5 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Combined with Valve & Meter, 6 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - 4 Valve Control Combined with Meter, 7 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Swash Plate (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Red Star-White Star Line (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Replacement, A Practical Reproach (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Royal Mail Steam Packet Company (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Russian Paper (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - School Catalogs (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Screw Thread Committee Minutes (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Screw Thread Division Prices, Costs, Methods (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Shop Arrangement (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Standards (Except Thread)
    - Standards & Codes, Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Standards, Tentative (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Swedish-American (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Tabulating Machine (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Thread Gaging (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Thread Standards, German (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Threads, Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Turret Lathes
    - Turret Lathes, American (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Turret Lathes, Foreign (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - United States Lines (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Weber, Richard & Company
    - Richard Weber, Letters pertaining to funds with (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - American Consulate, Weber (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Bauer & Schaurte, Weber (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Bohm, Franz, Weber (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Bureau of Foreign & Domestic Commerce, Weber (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Deutsche Bank and Discontogesellschaft, Weber (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Koyemann, M. m.b.h., Weber (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Peters, Arthur C. (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Screw Threads and Gear Cutting Standardization File
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineering
      - Standardization Committee, Main Committee (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Screw Thread Committee, Personnel (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Sub-committee
        - Scope, Arrangement, and Editing (Box 90, Folder 3)
        - Standard Threads Committee (Box 90, Folder 4)
        - Special Threads Committee (Box 90, Folder 5)
        - Acme Threads (Box 90, Folder 6)
        - Gages (Box 90, Folder 7)
        - Lag Screws (Box 90, Folder 8)
        - Field Survey (Box 90, Folder 9)
        - Screw Threads (Box 91, Folder 1)
        - Wood Screws (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Advertising
      - Competitors (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Die head Catalog Materials (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - New Material (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Old Material (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Automatic Lathe, work and sketch book (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Automatics, American (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Ball bearings (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Die heads (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Gear cutting (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Hydraulic design data (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Hydraulic pumps and motors, American (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Hydraulic pumps and motors, foreign (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - National Screw Thread Commission Bulletins (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Taps, miscellaneous (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Thread standards
      - American (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - American Petroleum Institute (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Old American (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - English (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Turret Lathe photo book (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Patent materials, drawings and descriptions
    - Patent materials, drawings and descriptions (Box 94)
- State Planning Board Files
  - Automobile Mileage Costs & Related Statistics State Department (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Clark, B. F. (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Basin (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut River Valley Water Resources Data (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Valley Interstate Flood Compact (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Dewey, James F. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Dummer, H. Boylston (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Fenton, Walter S. (Box 95, Folder 8-9)
  - Flood Control Committee
    - Hearing (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Legislation (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Maps & Charts (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Minutes (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - [General] (Box 96, Folder 2-3)
  - Garner, R. D. (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Graphic Survey (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Hayes, Helen (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Historical Publications, Committee on (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Hoke, Arthur S. (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Interstate Flood Compact (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Jones, A. E. (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Lord Charles (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Miller, R. J. (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - National Parks Commission (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Planning Board Expenses (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Report on Survey (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Shutler, Philip (Box 97, Folder 8-10)
  - Shepardson, F. W. (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
  - State Planning, Programs and Accomplishments (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Stevens, Robert (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - United States Engineer Office (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Vermont National Park Committee (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Vermont State Planning Board (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Vermont State Planning Board (Box 99, Folder 1-2)
  - Vermont, State of, Report of Special Commission to Study the Judicial System of Vermont (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Wilgus, Leonard W. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Wilner, E. R. (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Senatorial Correspondence
  - Agriculture (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture Ideas (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - American Association for the United Nations (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - American Research & Development Corporation, 1946-1949; 1951-1958 (Box 100, Folder 4-11)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineering (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - "American Society of Tool Engineers"- Honorary Membership (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Area Development (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Armed Forces (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Associated Press (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Austin, Warren R. (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Automobiles (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Bartlett, Howard C. (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Baruch, Bernard M. (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Batchelder Engineering Company (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Beacon Press (Box 101, Folder 11-12)
  - Beacon Press Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Bennett, F. M. (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Biographical Material, Ralph E. Flanders (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Blamont, Emile (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Block, Herbert (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Bole, Lyman W. (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Bosco, Giorgio (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Bowles, Chester (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - British Institution of Mechanical Engineers (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Burke Mountain (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Bush, Vannevar (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Business Advisory Council (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Byrd, Richard E. (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - B, Miscellaneous (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Cardigan Mountain School Corporation & Trustees (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Central Falls High School (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Chennault, Claire Lee (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Chiaramello, Domenico (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Christelow, Allan (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Civil War Centennial (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Clark, Grenville (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Clement, Frank G. (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1944; 1951-1958 (Box 102, Folder 11-14)
  - Committee for one million (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Courtesy & Membership Cards (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Cousins, Norman (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - C, Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth College, Amos Tuck School (Box 103, Folder 5-7)
  - Dartmouth Eye Institute (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Deale, Francis (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Disarmament & Atomic Control, A Special Proposal For Balanced (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Disarmament Historical Survey, United Nations (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - D, Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Economic Penetration (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Engineers' Club, New York City (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - E, Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Far Eastern Trip of 1955 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee Ideas (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Fletcher, L. J. (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Forestry (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - F, Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Germany (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Gourevitch, Boris (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - G, Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Gunther, John (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Hall of Fame at New York University (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Hall, Leonard W. (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Hammonds, G. Scott (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Hanna, Paul R. (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Hanover Institute (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Harriman, W. A. (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Harvard University, Honorary Degree (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Henderson, Arthur (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Hoffman, Paul (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Hogan, Pat (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Holt, Harold E. (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Hoover, Herbert (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Hsi-Sham, Marshall Yen (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - H, Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - Inflation (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Ingersoll, Roy C. (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - International Correspondence School (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - I, Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - India Trip (Box 106, Folder 5-6)
  - International Council for Christian Leadership (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Interparliamentary Union (Box 106, Folder 8-9)
  - Jones, Bassett (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Jones, F. Elwyn (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Jones & Lamson Machine Company
    - China's Tribute (Box 107, Folder 3)